<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Przemysl Guide!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="accomodation">ACCOMMODATION</string>
    <string name="culture">CULTURE</string>
    <string name="food_drinks"><![CDATA[FOOD & DRINKS]]></string>
    <string name="sightseeing">SIGHTSEEING</string>
    <string name="markettext">The houses in the Market Square of 16th-and 17th-c. origin which stand on three sides of the square (once they used to take all four sides). Most of the houses renovated in the 19th c. have retained the original arcades. Of note is also unique, sloping the Market Square itself, where once a Renaissance Town Hall stood, pulled down in 1812 by the Austrian authorities.</string>
    <string name="franciscantext">The Franciscan Church built in the 18th c. in place of an old Gothic church combines elements of the late Baroque and the Classicism. The church has an impressive rococo interior with an abundance of sculptures and frescoes.</string>
    <string name="fort11text">Fort XI Duńkowiczki was built between 1884 and 1886. It was almost identical with Fort XI "Orzechowce". However, it was modernized somewhat later. In the gun casemates added in the wings of the barracks newer-type cannons were placed. In the armoured batteries movable armoured turrets were added. The caponiers were not restructed.</string>
    <string name="archicatedraltext">The Roman-Catholic Archcathedral built in the Gothic style in the15th and 16th centuries in place of the older Romanesque one, whose remnants have been preserved in the vaults. It was renovated in the 18th c. in the Baroque style. Next to the cathedral there is the Bishop’s Palace and the late-Baroque 71-metre high belfry, a characteristic element of the Przemyśl panorama. In the upper part of the belfry, on the level of clock faces,  is a view point with a beautiful panorama of the city.</string>
    <string name="fort8text">KUŃKOWCE Fort VIII Łętownia. It dates back to the years 1854 to 1855, when the Austrians built one of their artillery earthworks on a hill west of Przemyśl. The fort obtained its present shape between 1881 and 1882.</string>
    <string name="casimircastletext">The Castle erected  after 1340 by King Casimirus the Great on the hill towering over the city in the place of an older settlement. In its yard one can fnd the remnants of the old rotunda and palatium from the time of King Bolesław I the Brave. The castle, thoroughly renovated in the 16th century in the Renaissance style now houses among others an auditorium of the Aleksander Fredro Amateur Drama Company, the oldest in Poland amateur drama group. In the vicinity of the castle, the beautifully situated Castle Park, which dates back to the year 1842, is worth seeing.</string>
    <string name="casimirtitle">Casimir Castle</string>
    <string name="fort8title">Fort VIII Łętownia in Kuńkowce</string>
    <string name="fort11title">Fort XI Duńkowiczki</string>
    <string name="archicatedtaltitle">The Roman-Catholic Archcathedral</string>
    <string name="franciscantitle">The Franciscan Church</string>
    <string name="markettitle">The houses in the Market Square</string>
    <string name="modkitch">Modern kitchen</string>
    <string name="tradkitch">Traditional polish kitchen</string>
    <string name="fuskitch">Fusion kitchen</string>
    <string name="galitkitch">Traditional galitian kitchen</string>
    <string name="fredtext">Small theatre located in Przemyśl Casimir Castle</string>
    <string name="fredtitle">Fredreum Theatre</string>
    <string name="belltext">located in the renovated Clock Tower at ul. Władycze.</string>
    <string name="beltitle">The Museum of Bells and Pipes</string>
    <string name="archimustitle">The Archicatedral Museum</string>
    <string name="archimustext">great collection of medieval sacral arts</string>
    <string name="strmustitle">The Przemysl Stronghold Museum</string>
    <string name="strmustext">museum dedicated to one of the greatest stronghold in 19th century Europe</string>
    <string name="natmustitle">National Museum of Przemysl</string>
    <string name="natmustext">The National Museum of the Przemyśl Land includes several branches. Its collections amount to more than 200 thousands exhibits from the area of archaeology, history, numismatics, art, ethnography and nature, more than 3,300 deposits and various auxiliary materials.</string>
    <string name="vbtext">Charming place located 6km from Przemyśl</string>
    <string name="zdtext">Old Polish Aristocracy Castle located 29km from Przemyśl</string>
    <string name="hktext">*** Hotel in old Palace</string>
    <string name="vbtitle">Hotel Villa Bolestraszyce</string>
    <string name="zdtitle">Zamek dubiecko</string>
    <string name="hktitle">Hotel Krasiczyn</string>
    <string name="boskotitle">Bosko</string>
    <string name="monarchiatitle">Monarchia</string>
    <string name="nagorcetitle">Na górce</string>
</resources>
